My name's Conan Edogawa!
اسمي إيدوغاوا كونان
High school student Shinichi was forced to take a drug that shrunk him.
أُجبر طالب الثانوية كودو شينتشي على تجرّع عقار قلص جسده
Although smaller, my mind remains that of a sharp detective!
،رغم أنّي أصبحت أصغر !لا يزال عقلي عقل متحرٍّ عظيم
Today's case takes place in a haunted house!
تقع أحداث قضيّة اليوم في منزلٍ مسكون
Even if it's hidden in an eerie basement, there's always only one truth!
،حتّى لو كانت مخفيةً في قبوٍ مخيف !تبقى الحقيقة واحدة دوماً
The Haunted House Murder.
جريمة قتل المنزل المسكون
Come ghost hunting with us, Conan-kun!
!رافقنا في صيد الأشباح يا كونان-كن
Ghost hunting?
صيد أشباح؟
Forget about him, Ayumi!
دعيه يا أيومي
Conan wouldn't be any help even if he did come!
فلن يفيدنا بشيء ولو أتى
But if it's just you and me who go...
...لكن إن كنتَ وأنا وحدنا من سنذهب
Where are these ghosts, anyway?
وأين تكون تلك الأشباح؟
An old mansion over on 4th Street!
منزل قديم في الشارع الرابع
4th Street?
الشارع الرابع؟
Yeah!
أجل
People call it a horror mansion
يدعوه الناس بقصر الرعب
because a man was beaten to death there 5 years ago!
لتعرض رجلٍ للضرب حتى الموت هناك !قبل خمسة أعوام
Come to think of it,
...صحيح
I do remember a mysterious incident occurring there...
أذكر حادثةً غامضة وقعت هناك
They say that after his wife and son moved out,
،يُقال أنّ زوجته وابنه قد انتقلا
evil spirits took up residence in the house!
!لكن سكنت الأرواح الشريرة المنزل
Evil spirits?
أرواح شريرة؟
Late at night, people've heard horrible moaning coming from inside,
سمع الناس عويلاً مخيفاً من الداخل ليلاً
stray dogs that wander inside are found as skeletons the next day,
وينتهي المطاف بالكلاب الضالة التي تدخل المكان هياكلاً عظمية اليوم التالي
and then last night, I saw a spirit ball in one of the windows!
!وفي ليلة البارحة، رأيتُ كرة روح عبر إحدى النوافذ
Well? Doesn't it make you excited?!
!ما رأيك؟ ألم تشعر بالحماس؟
That's nothing but nonsense.
هذه مجرد خرافات
In this scientific day and age, ghosts and monsters should be left
يجب أن تُترك الأشباح والأرواح للتلفاز والمانغا
to television and comic books.
في عصر العلم هذا
What? Are you calling Ayumi a liar?!
!ماذا؟ أتقصد أنّ أيومي كاذبة؟
No, I'm just--
...كلا، كنتُ فقط
Then come with us and prove that there aren't any ghosts!
سترافقنا إذاً وتثبت أنّ الأشباح !غير موجودة، واضح؟
After all, you shouldn't be scared one bit!
!لن أرحمك إن خفت
Eh? Me, come with you?
ماذا؟ أرافقكم؟
You believe me, don't you, Conan-kun?
تصدّقني يا كونان-كن، صحيح؟
Don't you?!
!صحيح؟
Yeah...
أجل
Okay, then!
!حسنٌ
Let's get ourselves ready and then beat up some ghosts!
!لنتجهز ونذهب نحن الأربعة لضرب الأشباح
Yeah!
!أجل
Are they being serious?!
أهو جاد؟
Let's all look at what we brought!
أخرجوا جميعاً ما جلبتموه
I brought a metal ghost-hunting bat!
!جلبتُ معي المضرب المعدني طارد الأشباح
I brought snacks for when we're hungry!
أحضرتُ معي طعاماً لوقت الجوع
I brought flashlights for everyone and a compass so we don't get lost.
وأحضرتُ مصابيح يدوية وبوصلةً كيلا نتوه
How about you, Conan-kun?
ماذا عنك يا كونان-كن؟
I didn't really bring anything...
لـ-لم أجلب شيئاً
It's your own fault if you die!
!إن متَ فهي مسؤوليتك أنت
Yeah! You'll get killed if you're careless!
!صحيح! سينالون منك إن استهترت
I'll try hard not to die...
...سأحاول ألّا أموت
Do these guys think they're entering a devil's castle or something?
أيظنّ هؤلاء أنهم يدخلون قلعة ملك الشياطين؟
Hey, this gate won't open...
هذه البوابة لا تُفتح
Don't worry.
لا تقلق
I found a secret entrance when I scouted out the place earlier!
وجدتُ حلّاً عندما أتيت ...لاستكشاف المكان قبلاً
A secret entrance?
مدخل سرّي؟
Hey! Here it is!
!ها هو
It's hidden by the grass,
تخفيه الأعشاب
but it's just big enough for someone to go through! See?
لكنه كبير بما يكفي ليعبر الناس، رأيتم؟
Amazing, Genta-kun!
!مذهل يا غينتا-كن
A secret entrance...
مدخل سرّي؟
Conan-kun! Hurry up!
!كونان-كن! أسرع
Right...
...أ-أجل
It's open!
إنّه مفتوح
It's too dark to see anything...
الظلام حالك، لا أرى شيئاً
It certainly is creepy...
...مريبٌ حقاً
Hey... maybe we should go home...
ر-ربما علينا العودة
See, it's even starting to rain...
فالمطر بدأ يهطل
Don't be stupid! We didn't come this far for nothing!
!حمقاء! لم نأت هنا لننسحب
You can go home by yourself if you want!
يمكنك أن ترجعي بمفردك إن أردتِ
You can't be serious!
!لكن
Lightning!
!رعد
Ayumi!
!أيومي
Look closer! It's just a sculpture of a demon!
أمعني النظر، إنّه مجرد تمثال شيطان
Aw, man! All I did was fall, but now my arms and legs are all dirty!
فظيع، سقطتُ فحسب لكن اتّسخت ساقيّ وذراعيّ بالكامل
Nobody's been here for a long time, so the floor's covered with dust...
لم يأت أحدٌ هنا لوقت طويل فالأرض مغطاة بالغبار
Here's a washroom!
!توجد مغسلة
Lucky!
!يا لحظّي
Walking around with you guys like this,
...المشي معكم هكذا
it's almost like we're in a role-playing game!
!يُشعرني أنّنا في لعبة تبادل أدوار
Yeah! We're in a party!
!أجل، نحن فرقة
I'm a brave fighter, of course!
!أنا البطل بالطبع
I'm a cute girl warrior!
!أنا المحاربة الظريفة
I'm a gifted magician!
أنا الساحر الذكيّ
I guess I'm a--
...أنا إذاً
You're a villager!
...أنت قرويّ
But villagers aren't party members!
لكن القرويين ليسوا أعضاءً في الفرقة
But you're an important character-- you give us information!
لكنّك شخصية مهمة تعطينا المعلومات
Yeah! It's the perfect role for you!
أجل، دورٌ مثاليّ لك
Bah! Don't patronize me!
!لا تستخفوا بي
What's the deal, you guys? Hiding behind the villager, are you?
ما خطبكم؟ تختبئون وراء ظهر القرويّ؟
Get moving, villager!
!اذهب يا قرويّ
Conan-kun! You can do it!
!أنتَ لها يا كونان-كن
I see. The door opened by itself because of the wind.
فهمت، فتحت الرياح الباب
This is what most "ghosts" turn out to be.
هكذا تكون حقيقة معظم الأشباح
You almost sound like a detective, Mitsuhiko-kun!
تبدو كمتحرٍّ يا ميتسوهيكو-كن
You guys wait here-- I need to use the restroom.
سأذهب لدورة المياه لذا انتظروا هنا
Will you be alright by yourself?
ستكون بخيرٍ بمفردك؟
Of course! I have science and logic on my side!
!بالطبع، فالعلم والمنطق في صفيّ
Man, this house sure is huge!
يا له من منزلٍ كبير
A really rich person must've lived here!
كان يعيش هنا رجلٌ فاحش الثراء بالتأكيد
Ghosts can't possibly exist in this scientific day and age!
لا يمكن أن توجد الأشباح ...في عصر العلم هذا
That was probably the sound of wind blowing through a small hole
لا بد أنّه كان صوت هبوب الرياح عبر فتحة صغيرة
or something...
وما شابه
Alright! I'll check for myself!
!حسنٌ، سأرى بنفسي
These stairs go into the basement...
...تقود هذه الأدراج للقبو
Those sounds are coming from down there...
سمعتُ الصوت من الأسفل
Alright, then...
...حـ-حسنٌ
Mitsuhiko-kun's taking a long time...
تأخّر ميتسوهيكو-كن
It's been twenty minutes...
مضت 20 دقيقة
Maybe he's going Number 2!
ربما يتغوّط
The sound's getting louder...
الصوت يرتفع
It's coming from that room!
يصدر من تلك الغرفة
That was Mitsuhiko's voice!
!ذاك صوت ميتسوهيكو
Wait, Conan-kun!
!انتظر يا كونان-كن
There really is something in this mansion!
!يوجد شيءٌ في هذا القصر بالفعل
Hey, Mitsuhiko! Where are you?!
ميتسوهيكو! أين أنت؟
Say something! Mitsuhiko-kun!
!أجبنا! ميتسوهيكو-كن
Where could he have gone?!
أين ذهب؟
He wasn't in the bathroom, either...
لم يكن في الحمّام أيضاً
That scream was no joke!
لم يكن ذاك الصراخ بسيطاً
Something must've happened to Mitsuhiko!
حلّ أمرٌ ما بميتسوهيكو
Alright, then...
...حسنٌ
You two hide in a nearby room!
!اختبئا في غرفة مجاورة
I'm going to look for Mitsuhiko!
سأبحث عن ميتسوهيكو
Listen to me! Don't leave the room, no matter what!
!إيّاكما أن تغادرا
Hey! Conan!
!كونان
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Something's not right!
غريب
Supposedly no one's lived here ever since the murder,
يُفترض أنّ لا أحد يعيش هنا ،مذ وقعت الحادثة
so why isn't the water turned off?!
فلمَ الماء يصبّ؟
There's also that room with the open window!
كما الغرفة بالنافذة المفتوحة
The room hadn't been damaged by wind or rain at all!
لم تكن بها آثار ضرر من الرياح أو المطر
That means the window must've been opened fairly recently!
مما يعني أنّها فُتحت مؤخراً نسبياً
And then there's that secret entrance that was built out of plain view!
وذاك المدخل السرّي الذي صُنع خارج مرأى الجميع
Someone's been coming into and leaving this mansion!
هناك من يدخل ويغادر هذا القصر
But who?!
لكن من؟
And what for?!
ولمَ؟
Our moms must be worrying about us right about now...
لا بد أنّ أمهاتنا يشعرن بالقلق علينا الآن
It's already night outside...
الظلام مخيم في الخارج
Conan sure is taking a long time...
تأخّر كونان حقاً
These aren't for you!
!لا يمكنك أخذ هذه
Mitsuhiko-kun is probably lost and hungry!
ميتسوهيكو-كن تائه في مكانٍ ما ويتضور جوعاً حتماً
Conan-kun too...
...كونان-كن أيضاً
These are for them! You can't have them!
!هذه لهما! لا يمكنك أكلها
Fine...
فـ-فهمت
I smell food!
!أشتم رائحة طعام
It's coming from down there...
من ذاك الاتجاه
I'm gonna check it out!
سأذهب للتفقد
No! Conan-kun said not to leave!
!لا يمكنك! أخبرنا كونان-كن ألّا نغادر
I'll be right back!
سأعود فوراً
Genta-kun!
!غينتا-كن
That's strange! There're no signs of anybody anywhere!
غريب، لا علامات على وجود أحد في أيّ مكان
Maybe there's really nobody here?!
ربما لا يوجد شخص حقاً؟
A photograph...
...صورة
Is this the mansion's owner who was killed 5 years ago?
أهذا مالك القصر الذي قُتل قبل خمسة أعوام؟
And is that his wife and son behind him?
ومن خلفه هما زوجته وابنه؟
I thought that the killer was never caught,
...ظننتُ أنّ القاتل لم يُقبض عليه
and that the remaining family members moved away...
...وانتقل أفراد العائلة المتبقين
That was Genta's voice!
!كان ذلك صوت غينتا
Dammit! I told him to hide!
!تبّاً! أخبرته أن يختبئ
Genta-kun! Stop trying to scare me!
!غينتا-كن! لا تخفني هكذا
Wait! Those aren't Genta-kun's footsteps!
!كلا! ليست هذه خطوات غينتا-كن
Then whose are they?!
!من إذاً؟ من؟
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Don't make any sounds!
!لا تصدري صوتاً
Here they come!
إنّه قادم
It's a ghost!
شـ-شبح
No, look closer! It's a person!
!كلا، أمعني النظر! إنّه إنسان
They're just taking something somewhere!
ينقل شيئاً ما
But where to?!
لكن أين؟
Wait, Conan-kun!
!انتظر يا كونان-كن
They're gone!
!اختفى
There aren't any rooms around here,
لا توجد غرف في الجوار
...and straight ahead is a dead-end!
والطريق مسدود أمامنا
So where did that person disappear to?!
أين اختفى؟
I told you it was a ghost!
!أخبرتك أنّه شبح
The dust on the floor has a line in it!
يوجد خطّ على الغبار في الأرض
Wait a second! Maybe this is a--
...لحظة، أيمكن
There's a door here.
هذا باب
Yeah! That person just now went down through it!
!فهمت، نزل ذاك الشخص هنا
No good! It's too much for a kid to open!
لا جدوى، لا يمكنني رفعه بقوّة صبي
I know!
!صحيح
I call these Retractable Suspenders.
أسميّها الحمّالات القابلة للسحب
One push of a button and they retract from their stretched-out state.
بضغطة واحدة تتكمّش من حالتها المتمددة
They should work great for tying up criminals!
!ستفيدك في ربط المجرمين
Yeah! I'll try using these!
أجل، سأجرب استعمالها
What are you going to do with them?
ماذا ستفعل بها؟
Just watch and see!
راقبي فقط
Awesome!
!مُذهل
A staircase to the basement!
!درج للقبو
Maybe Mitsuhiko and Genta are down here!
لعلّ ميتسوهيكو وغينتا في الأسفل
I see light!
!أرى ضوءاً
A prison cell!
!زنزانة
What's it doing here?!
لمَ توجد واحدة هنا؟
There's someone in there! Look, on the bed!
!يوجد شخص! انظر، على السرير
Who is this guy?!
من هذا الشخص؟
Someone's coming!
!أحدهم قادم
Another bad dream?
كابوس آخر؟
You poor thing...
...يا للمسكين
But that was over 5 years ago-- forget about it already!
،لكن وقع ذلك قبل 5 أعوام !فلتنس أمره وحسب
No matter how much you suffer, it still won't bring him back to life...
مهما عانيتَ فلن يرجع الموتى
Back to life?!
الموتى؟
Could she be referring to the murdered owner of this house?!
أيمكن أنّها تقصد مالك هذا المنزل المقتول؟
If so, then these two people are--
...مما يعني أنّ هذين الاثنين
Eat up.
هيّا، كُل
I'm not keeping you locked up down here to make you suffer, you know!
!لا أحتجزك هنا كي تعاني
Akio! I'm doing this so that you'll have a future!
!أكيو! أفعل هذا لتحظى بمستقبل
Aha, now I see the truth behind this mansion and that murder!
فهمت الآن سرّ هذا القصر !وحقيقة تلك الجريمة
It sounds like we have some more rats that snuck in with the other two...
يبدو أنّه تسللت جرذان أخرى مع الجرذين السابقين
Show yourself. There's no point in hiding!
اظهروا، لا جدوى من الاختباء
Come out!
!اظهروا
No point in hiding...
...لا جدوى من الاختباء
You're the one who should come out of hiding, ma'am!
!هذا موجّه لك يا سيّدة
I found it in the study earlier...
وجدتُها في المكتب قبل قليل
The photograph of you and this house's owner,
صورتك ومالك هذا المنزل
who was murdered 5 years ago.
الذي قُتل قبل 5 أعوام
His appearance has drastically changed in the 5 years he's lived down here,
كما من تغيّر مظهره بشكل جذري في الخمسة أعوام التي قضاها هنا
but the man standing next to you in the picture is your son--
...الشاب الذي كان بجوارك في الصورة هو ابنك
the man in that prison cell!
!أجل، المحتجز في تلك الزنزانة
The mole below his eye was the only thing that couldn't change.
الشامة تحت عينه كانت الشيء الوحيد الذي لم يتغير
I thought something was strange when I first entered the house.
شعرتُ أن هناك أمراً غريباً مُذ دخلت القصر
The family moved out so the mansion should've been empty,
يُفترض أنّ العائلة انتقلت وأصبح القصر فارغاً
but there was still running water.
لكن كان الماء لا يزال يجري مع ذلك
After all, nobody is so frivolous as to continually pay the water bill
فلا أحد مستهتر كفاية ليدفع فاتورة الماء باستمرار
for a house that no one lives in.
لبيت لا يعيش فيه أحد
And then there's that discretely placed entrance.
كما هناك موضوع المدخل المخبأ
Compared to the age of the surrounding walls,
كان لا يزال ذاك الباب الخشبي جديداً
that wooden door was still new.
مقارنةً بعمر الجدران المجاورة
My guess is that it was built after the incident...
صُنع بعد وقوع الحادثة غالباً
...so that you could enter and leave the mansion without being seen.
كي يمكنك الدخول والمغادرة دون أن يراك أحد
But as for why it was necessary to make the place look uninhabited,
لكن سبب حرصك على جعل المكان يبدو غير مسكون
and why you needed to keep your son locked up in the basement...
...واحتجازك لابنك في القبو
...those questions were answered by your conversation just now!
تبيّن لي من محادثتكما قبل قليل
Who are you?!
!من أنت؟ من أنت؟
Conan Edogawa. A detective.
إيدوغاوا كونان، مُتحرٍّ
A detective?!
!مُتحرٍّ؟
There are two possibilities that I can think of.
يوجد احتمالان يمكنني التفكير بهما
The first is that the house's owner was killed by you, his wife,
الأول هو أن مالك المنزل قُتل ،بواسطتك أنت، زوجته
and that you locked your son up because he witnessed the murder.
وسجنتِ ابنك لأنّه شهد الجريمة
The second possibility is that it was your son who killed your husband!
!والثاني أنّ ابنك من قتل زوجك
Knowing that he was the killer,
،بعلمك أنّه القاتل
you decided to protect your son by hiding the truth behind the murder.
قرّرتِ حماية ابنك بإخفاء حقيقة الجريمة
But the weight of what he had done was too much for him.
لكنّ عبء الذنب كان ثقيلاً عليه
The moans coming from this mansion were probably his deranged screams.
العويل الصادر من القصر كان صرخاته المتشققة غالباً
Your son probably wanted to turn himself in to atone for his crime.
أراد ابنك تسليم نفسه للتكفير عن جريمته على الأرجح
But you couldn't allow that to happen.
لكنك أبيتِ السماح بذلك
Try to understand! This is all for your sake!
!حاول أن تفهم! هذا لأجلك
Yes. You didn't want your son to be known as a criminal,
أجل، لم تريدي أن يُعتبر ابنك مجرماً
so you chose to keep him concealed here in absolute confinement.
فاخترتِ إخفاءه هنا دون السماح له بأخذ خطوة خارجاً
Judging from your conversation just now and from your reaction,
...من محادثتكما قبل قليل وردّة فعلكما
your husband's killer must have been--
...أرجّح أنّ قاتل زوجك كان
Shut up!
!ا-اخرس! اخرس
Stop!
!توقفي
Stop, Mom! He's exactly right!
!توقفي يا أمّي! إنّه محق
That's right! I was the one who killed Dad!
!صحيح، كنتُ من قتل أبي
Akio!
أكيو
It happened on a spring night 5 years ago...
وقع الأمر في ليلة ربيع قبل 5 أعوام
I had just failed my third college entrance exam...
...فشلتُ في امتحان القبول الجامعي للمرة الثالثة
What? You failed another one?!
ماذا؟ فشلت مجدداً؟
You're an embarrassment to your family!
!أنت عار على عائلتك
You're pathetic! You're a waste of a person!
!بل نكرة! أنت نكرة
I was already very mentally anguished,
...كنتُ متمزقاً ذهنياً
so when I heard those words come from my father...
...فعندما سمعت كلمات أبي
...I lost control of myself for a split second!
فقدتُ السيطرة على نفسي للحظة
Akio!
!أكيو
When I came to, I was holding a blood-smeared candlestick in my hands,
عندما استعدتُ وعيي، كنتُ أحمل شمعداناً مغطّى بالدماء
and my father was lying there on the floor, nearly unrecognizable!
وأبي طريحاً غير واضح الملامح
Don't you worry! I'll protect you!
لا تقلق، سأحميك
Mom!
!أمّي
The rest was just as you said.
الباقي كما قلت
My mom made it look like a robber killed him
جعلت أُمي الحادثة كأنها جريمة سطو
and then she stuck me in this cell.
واحتجزتني في هذه الزنزانة
But I can't stand it any longer! I can't live like this anymore,
لكن لم أعد أحتمل! لا أستطيع العيش
constantly haunted by the murder of my own father!
!وذنب قتل أبي يطاردني
I want to confess my crime so I can live with myself!
!أريد الاعتراف بجريمتي كي أعيش بسلام مع نفسي
Get a hold of yourself, Akio!
!تماسك يا أكيو
Hang in there until the statute of limitations runs out!
!تحمّل حتى ينتهي الحدّ الزمني
If we keep quiet, nobody will ever know!
لـ-لن يعرف أحد إن لزمنا الصمت
Yes, if you remain in hiding like this, you will be able to escape the police.
معكِ حق، سيفلت من الشرطة إن واصل الاختباء هكذا
But you'll never escape from the guilt!
!لكنه لن يستطيع الهروب من ذنبه أبداً
Ma'am.
أمّاه
Do you intend to keep this heavy weight on your son
أتنوين جعل ابنك يتحمّل هذا العبء
for the rest of his life?
الثقيل لبقية حياته؟
The night of terror came to an end,
،انتهت ليلة الرعب
and bright sunlight lit up the mansion.
وأشرق ضوء الشمس على القصر
The two who disappeared during the night
من اختفيا البارحة
were found sleeping amiably in the grass outside.
كانا نائمين بين الأعشاب خارجاً
Apparently the woman had put them to sleep with an anesthetic
يبدو أنّ الأم نوّمتهما بمخدر
and threw them out of the house.
وألقتهما خارجاً
That same day, the son and wife turned themselves in to the authorities,
سلّمت نفسها وابنها في اليوم نفسه للسلطات
and a baffling murder case came to an end after 5 long years.
وُحلّت القضيّة المحيرة بعد 5 أعوام طويلة
Naturally, the four of us were scolded by the grownups...
تعرضنا الأربعة لتوبيخ شديد من البالغين بالطبع
I sure wish I was back in my normal body.
أتمنى لو أرجع لجسدي الطبيعي
Another haunted house?!
!منزل مسكون آخر؟
Yeah! Ayumi found another one!
أجل، وجدت أيومي منزلاً آخر
This one's on 2nd Street, and it belonged to the Eto family!
!إنّه في الشارع الثاني ويخصّ عائلة إيتو
Eto?
إيتو؟
People living in the area say it's a spooky mansion filled with weird books,
يقول أهل الحيّ أنّ ذاك القصر المريب مليء بالكتب الغريبة
and a boy who used to live there by himself was eaten by some monsters!
!والفتى الذي كان يعيش بمفرده أكلته الوحوش
A boy who lived by himself in a spooky mansion filled with books?
فتى يعيش بمفرده في قصر مريب مليء بالكتب؟
2nd Street? Eto?
الشارع الثاني؟ إيتو؟
Say, are you sure the name was Eto?
أأنتِ متأكدة أن الاسم كان إيتو؟
Yeah! You write it with a katakana "E" and a kanji "TO"!
"أجل، تكتبه بكاتاكانا "إي" وكانجي "تو
Okay! Let's get ready to beat up some more ghosts!
!حسناً! لنتجهز لهجوم آخر
Wait! That's not "Eto"! That's "Kudo"!
!"انتظروا! تلك ليست "إيتو"، بل "كودو
That's my house!
!إنّه منزلي
Let's go, villager!
!هيّا بنا أيّها القرويَ
He's dead!
!إنّه ميت
We need to contact the police!
يجب الاتصال بالشرطة
This is the knife they used during filming!
هذه... السكّين التي اُستعملت في التصوير
Which means the killer was someone on the staff!
مما يعني أنّ القاتل أحد العمّال
That's it!
!فهمت! هكذا إذاً
Now I know the truth behind this incident!
!عرفت حقيقة هذه القضية
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
The TV Drama Murder Case.
جريمة قتل الدراما التلفزية
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Fu dog.
كلب أسد